（上条(かみじょう)）
フガッ…
Shit, a nosebleed...
（上条）
ヤベッ… 鼻血
There's a reason why the bathroom is my bedroom every night.
俺が毎晩 こんな所で
眠っているのには理由がある
（滑る音）
いてっ！
Ow!
ウウッ… ティッシュ ティッシュ
Tissue... Tissue...
My original sleeping spot, my bed,
本来の寝床であるベッドが―
is currently occupied by a peculiar, sassy little girl.
目下 奇妙な居候の
占領下に置かれているのだ
As to whom the location truly belongs,
誰かの居場所が
空けてあるっぽい気がするが―
I decide to not dwell on it.
あえて 考えないことにする
（上条）ゲッ…
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）ウ… ウ～ン…
Touma?
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）
当麻(とうま)？
Sorry, did I wake you up?
（上条）
あっ 悪い 起こしちまったか
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）
アア？　ウ… ウン…
えっと…
当麻 念のために聞くけど―
Umm, Touma, just to be sure,
何しに こんな所まで来たの？
what are you doing all the way over here?
何しにって 単に俺は 鼻血…
What am I doing, you ask?
I'm just here...
...to clean my nose-
か… 勘違いしてもらっちゃ困るな
Hey, don't be getting the wrong idea here!
A manga-like sequence of "nosebleed - excitement"-
鼻血 イコール 興奮なんて
漫画的な…
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）当麻！
（上条）えっ？
Touma!
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）
天にまします我らの父に誓って
言える？
Will you swear in the name of our Father in Heaven?
That you do not feel anything when you see my sleeping figure-
私の寝顔を見たって
何も感じないって
What are you talking about?
何言ってんだか
Of course I don't feel anything by seeing your sleeping fig-
お前の寝顔なんか見たって
何にも感じないに決まって…
（上条）アアッ！
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）何にも？
You don't feel anything?!
何にも感じないって
どういうこと？
What do you mean you don't feel anything?!
私は これでも女の子なのであって
Don't you realize that "Hey, she's actually a girl",
少しは そういう感情も
抱いてくれなければ―
that if you don't carry a bit of shame in this act,
that I would be in shock?!
ショックを
受けてしまうというのに！
That's what you care about?!
（上条）
そっちか！
In all honesty, I, Kamijyo Touma,
実を言うと 私 上条当麻は―
あなたの寝顔を見て
不覚にも ときめいてしまいました
after seeing your sleeping figure,
got a bit excited just now!
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）
今更 そんな覆された発言を
信じろっていうのがムリなんだよ！
Coming back with that now and asking me to believe that is out of the question!
Ah-
「数学計算問題集」
Math Exercises Workbook...
Roughly 24 hours before the end of summer vacation...
（上条）
夏休みの終わりまで
おおよそ24時間
That reminds me, I don't recall me ever taking a stab at the biggest obstacles to...
そういえば
夏休みの宿題なんていう―
最大の足かせに
手をつけている場面は…
complete... summer vacation... freedom...
なかった… ような… 気がする
Such misfortune...
不幸だ
#18 Replica
Faker
～♪
（美琴(みこと)）
アア… 夏休みも今日で終わりかぁ
Ahh, and summer vacation ends today.
（舞夏(まいか)）御坂(みさか) 御坂
（美琴）うん？
Misaka, Misaka.
You look like you have a lot of time on your hands.
（舞夏）相変わらず暇そうだな
（美琴）まあね
Yeah.
一応 あんたは
メイドさん見習いなんだから―
But as a maid apprentice, you realize you shouldn't be talking as an equal toward your seniors.
タメ口はマズイっしょ
If you're going to the convenience store, I'd like you to buy me a manga.
もし コンビニ行くなら
漫画を買ってきてほしい
It's one that isn't rated 18+ but still very steamy.
18禁ではないものの
妙に なまめかしいやつ
あんたって
ボーイズラブとか好きなんだっけ？
You like Boys Love stuff, right?
Oh, you know me...
（舞夏）
私は あれだよ あれ
I love the genre where a brother and a sister fall into a deep and muddy romance.
兄と妹でドロドロになるやつが好き
Yeah, yeah.
（海原(うなばら)）おはようございます
（美琴）ウッ…
Good morning.
（海原）
御坂さんじゃないですか
これから どちらへ？
Why if it isn't Misaka-san?
Where are you headed to?
If you don't mind, may I accompany you part of the way?
よろしければ 自分も途中まで
ご一緒しても かまいませんか？
Unabara... Mitsuki...
（美琴）
海原光貴(みつき)…
（海原）
あれ？　もしかして
気分でも すぐれませんか？
Are you not feeling well?
Ah, no...
あ～… いや…
（美琴）
こいつ この１週間 毎日毎日…
Every single day of this week, this guy...
If you'd like, I know a nice seafood restaurant in the neighborhood.
もし よろしければ―
近所に魚料理の
おいしいお店があるのですが
朝食の直後に 食事に誘うんかい
Does it make sense to ask someone out for a meal right after breakfast?
ああ… 誘ってくれるのは
うれしいんだけど―
I'm glad you asked me, but I have something to do, too...
私にも用事があるというか…
I'll come with you.
ご一緒しますよ
Yeah, I was thinking about going to
the lingerie section of the department store.
そう！　デパートの
下着売り場まで出かけようかと
You know, not exactly a comfortable place for guys to go, right?
ほら
男の人には つらい場所でしょう？
（海原）
ご一緒しますよ
I'll go with you.
I can't say it...
言えない
I can't say that I'm going to read manga for free in the convenience store.
これからコンビニに
立ち読みに行くなんて言えない
（上条）頼む このとおり！
（美琴）あっ…
Please, I beg you!
It's okay, Kami-yan.
（青髪ﾋﾟｱｽ）
ええやん カミやん
放課後には漏れなく―
A healthy dose of Komoe-sensei's private tutoring is waiting for you after school.
小萌(こもえ)先生の
個人授業が ついてくるんやで
If a girl falls from the sky due to us helping you with your homework,
（土御門(つちみかど)）
カミやんの宿題 手伝って
空から女の子が降ってくるなら―
喜んでアシストするけどにゃ～
then I'd be glad to provide you with my assistance.
The type of girls you guys are interested in are sky girls?
（上条）
お前たちの好みの…
（美琴）
そうだ ほかの男と
待ち合わせしてることにしよう
Oh yeah, I'll pretend I'm waiting for another guy!
ごめ～ん 待った？
So~rry~ have you been waiting for me?
（青髪ﾋﾟｱｽ）
ハッ…
何を言うてん カミやんは
What are you talking about, Kami-yan?
Not only do I like girls that fall from the sky,
僕は落下型ヒロインのみならず―
I also like maid girls, military girls, shrine maidens,
メイド 軍人 巫女(みこ)さん 婦警
ショタコン ツンデレ…
shotacons, tsunderes, cheerleaders,
yanderes, clumsy girls, robot girls-
（青髪ﾋﾟｱｽ）
ドジっ子 ロボット娘…
（美琴）
“待った？”って
言ってんでしょうが！
I said, "HAVE YOU BEEN WAITING FOR ME"!!!
無視すんなよ こら！
Don't ignore me, idiot!!!
ンンッ… く… くそ… 誰だ？
Damn it, who is it?
…て ビリビリ！
Wha- Shocker?
Please, play along.
（美琴）お願い 話を合わせて
（上条）はぁ？
（美琴）
アハハハッ… ごめん 遅れちゃって
Sorry for being late.
I'll repay you by treating you to something, so forgive me.
おわびに何か おごってあげるから
それで許して　ねえ？
Pretty please.
Huh?
はい？
What?
（女子生徒）
えっ なに あれ？
（女子生徒）あれ 御坂さん
（女子生徒）あっ ホントだ
Isn't that Misaka-san?
Wow!
（女子生徒たち）
すご～い！
How bold of her...
（寮監）
面白い　寮の眼前で
逢(あ)い引(び)きとは いい度胸だ
...to be rendezvousing in front of the dormitory...
Excuse me?!
（黒子(くろこ)）
ちょっと！　私に無断で
何をやってるんですの お姉様！
What are you doing without getting my consent, Oneesama?!
What's going on?!
何だよ いきなり
人を全速力で引きずり回し…
Dragging someone at full speed-
（美琴）うるさい！
（上条）ああ？
Be quiet!!!
Just shut up, please, and let me think through what just happened!!!
黙って！　お願いだから
少し気持ちの整理をさせて～！
（海原）
つまり この１週間―
In other words, you've been stalked around by this Unabara dude every day this week.
その海原ってヤツに
毎日 付きまとわれていたと
That's right.
（美琴）
そうなのよ
ウチの学校の
理事長の孫だっていうし
He's the grandson of our school's superintendent,
無下(むげ)にもできなくてさ
so I can't just drop him.
And now, you grab whoever you can to pretend he's
your boyfriend in order try to get away from that guy.
（上条）
…で 誰でもいいから恋人役にして
そいつから離れようとしたと
What will you have me do then?
しょうがないじゃない
You just happened to walk by.
あんたが
ちょうど通りがかったんだから
ふ～ん… とりあえず
離れることはできたんだろう
Well, you got away from that guy for now.
だったら もう
演技する必要はねえんじゃねえの？
So, there's no need to be acting anymore, right?
う～ん… せっかくの機会だから
But I'd like to take this chance firmly and
make sure he doesn't harass me anymore.
二度と付きまとわれないように
したいんだけど…
“したいんだけど”？
You'd like to, but...
I'll have to be with you all day and
make sure as many people as possible see us.
今日１日
あんたと一緒に行動して―
それをできるだけ
多くの人に見てもらう
That way, Unabara-
（美琴）それで海原は…
（上条）ハァ…
What's the matter?
…て どうしたの？
不幸だ…
Such misfortune...
…で
何か質問とか感想とかって ある？
And?
You have any thoughts or questions for me?
感想ね…
Thoughts, eh?
とりあえず 鼻に
ついてるマスタードは拭いとけよ
For starters, wipe the mustard off your nose.
（美琴）アアッ！　ウウッ…
（上条）もしも～し？
Hello?
（美琴）ウッ…
（上条）大丈夫か？
You all right?
Of-course-I-am...
（美琴）
大丈夫よ　決まってんでしょう
（美琴）あれ？
（上条）うん？
Which one's yours?
あんたのって どっちだっけ？
さあ？　多分 こっちだと…
Beats me.
It's probably this-
Let-
（美琴）ちょっと見せて！
（上条）はぁ？
Let me see first.
Are you able to tell?
分かったのか？
（上条）分かった…
（美琴）もう分かんないわよ！
If you are-
Ahh, I don't know, all right?!
じゃ あんたが こっち
私が これでいい
You eat this one!
And I'll take this one!
Gosh!
…たく ちょっとは気にしなさいよ
このバカ！
Show a little concern at least!
You idiot!
We ordered the same item, didn't we?
別に 注文したのって
同じメニューなんだろう
（上条）うん？　どうしたんだお前
（美琴）えっ？
What's wrong?
借りてきた猫みたいに
You're like a gentle kitten, now.
（美琴）
何でもない
It's nothing...
…で 何すりゃいいんだ？
So, what do I need to do?
えっ？　何って？
What are you talking about?
Well, what should I do so that we look like a couple?
だからさ 一体 何をやれば
恋人っぽく見えるわけ？
In the end, less than ten Sisters remain in
Academy City after the end of the experiment.
（美琴）
結局 実験のあとに
学園都市に残った妹達(シスターズ)って―
10人も いないのよね
Most of them went to institutions outside of the City,
ほとんどは
学園都市の外にある機関で―
体の調整をやってるみたい
adjusting their bodies or what not.
そんじゃ 連中も何だかんだで
元気に やってるわけか
So at least they're doing well.
That's good, that's good.
良かった 良かった
これ 恋人同士の会話とは
違わないかしら？
Isn't this different from what couples usually chat about?
（上条）
う～ん… 違うかな？
Is it?
あのね
女を無視して勉強するって―
Hello?
Ignoring the girl and doing homework?
どこが恋人同士に見えるってのよ？
How exactly is this like a couple?
I haven't finished my homework.
こっちは宿題が終わってないんだよ
タイムリミットまで
24時間 切ってんだぞ
I have less than 24 hours before the deadline, okay?
Homework?
宿題？　ああ… 聞いたことあるわ
Ah, I've heard of such a thing.
…て 常盤台(ときわだい)には ないのかよ？
Wha- Tokiwadai has no homework?!
ねえ どんなの やってんの？
Hey, what kind of questions do they ask?
H-Hey...
（上条）
お… おい…
ふ～ん…
要するに単なる復習なのね
So, it's just a type of review.
（上条）
あの… なんで解けるの？
How can you solve it?
Why can't you solve it?
（美琴）
なんで あんたは解けないのよ？
まあまあ ちょっとは気分転換に
ジュースとか飲んじゃう？
There, there.
How about we switch gears and get drinks or something?
I'll go buy them.
（美琴）私 買ってくるけど
（上条）あっ…
あっ いや 俺が行くって
No, I'll go.
私が行くってったら私が行くの
I said I'll go, and so I will.
こういうのは
断ったほうが気まずくなんのよ
Saying no in these cases will make things worse.
（海原）
はじめまして え～っと…
Pleased to meet you, umm...
Kamijyo Touma.
（上条）上条当麻だけど
（海原）自分は海原光貴といいます
My name is Unabara Mitsuki.
（上条）…で 俺に何の用なんだ？
（海原）あの…
So, what do you need from me?
Are you Misaka-san's friend?
あなたは
御坂さんのお友達なんですか？
Does it bug you?
（上条）
気になんの？
（海原）
ええ　自分の好きな人の
そばにいる男性となれば当然
Yes, if it's a man close to the girl I like, of course.
（海原）
だから 御坂さんは
もっと 人に対して―
That's why I think Misaka-san should make it clearer to others whether she likes or dislikes someone.
好きと嫌いを
はっきり言うべきだと思うんですよ
Ah, the answer for that question is 3.
あっ そこの問題の答えは３です
You think so?
（上条）
そっか？　かなり自分の感情に
素直だと思うけど
I think she's pretty straight with her feelings.
To be honest, I don't think I've ever heard her true voice.
正直 自分は
あの人の本音というものを―
一度も聞いたことはない気がします
Oh, the answer is 4 for that one.
えっと そこの答えは４です
２は引っ掛けですね
2's a trap.
Hrm, I think you're right, actually.
ふ～ん…
言われてみりゃ そうかもな
Yes, I am.
そうですよ まったく
（上条）
どうしたんだ？　お前
What's wrong?
Let me borrow you for a moment.
ちょっと一緒に来なさい
What's the point if you become friends with him?!
（美琴）
あんたが
あいつと仲良くなってちゃ―
意味ないでしょうが！
いい？　あんたは今 私の こ…
You understand?
Right now, you're my boy-
恋人役なの！
...boyfriend character!
それは付きまとってくる海原光貴を
諦めさせるためのものなの！
It's for chasing away Unabara Mitsuki, who keeps stalking me!
この基本だけは忘れないでよ！
Don't forget this basic principle!
No can do.
（上条）ムリ
（美琴）えっ？
He's a good guy.
（上条）
あいつ 結構 いいヤツだぜ
お前のことも本気だった
And he's serious about you.
What's that supposed to mean?
（美琴）
なによ？　それ…
（上条）
あいつの何が気に入らないんだ？
What do you not like about him?
Well, there's something wrong about
going out with someone you don't like.
まあ 好きでもないのに
つきあうってのも なんだけどさ
You-
あんたは…
（美琴）
そうよね 何でもないわ
You're right.
Nothing.
And, what are you going to do now?
（上条）
…で どうするんだ？
まだ続けるのか？
Are we continuing this? Or-
（上条）それとも…
（美琴）んじゃ…
We'll stop pretending to be a couple.
これで恋人ごっこは終わり
最後に何か おごってあげるわよ
なに食べたい？
Let me treat you to something before we leave.
What would you like?
You still want to eat?
（上条）
まだ食うのかよ？
（美琴）
どこも満席か　う～ん…
Everywhere's full...
How about that?
（美琴）
あれでいい？　いいわよね
何か適当に買ってくるから
It's okay, right?
I'll just buy something.
あっ… おい 御坂！
Hey, Misaka!
（海原）あれ？　お１人ですか？
（上条）うん？
Are you by yourself?
Was she done with her business?
用というのは もうお済みで？
Ah, Misaka's struggling inside...
御坂なら あの中で格闘中…
（上条）うん？
（海原）どうかしました？
What's wrong?
（上条）
なあ お前 兄弟とかっているのか？
Hey, do you have a brother or anything?
No, I'm a single child.
（海原）
いえ 一人っ子ですけど
今 お前と よく似たヤツが
入ってったから…
Well, someone that looks like you went in...
（女性）えっ？　ちょっと…
（美琴）ウ～ 暑い
It's so hot...
（美琴）ちょっと あんた なに…
（海原）逃げてください！
Hey, what are you-
Run!
（海原）
自分そっくりの人が
あの店に入っていったんですか？
A person who looks like me went into that store, eh?
Like you? I think he looked just like you.
（上条）
似てたっつうか
瓜二(うりふた)つだったように見えたけど
肉体を他人の姿に
変化させる能力者だっています
There are espers that can change the appearance of their body.
Perhaps he is pretending to be me and trying to get close to Misaka-san.
自分に化けて 御坂さんに
近づこうとしているのかも
まあ あいつも
ちょっとした有名人だしな
Well, she is quite the popular one.
Would you mind going to take a look?
ちょっと見てきてもらえませんか？
自分は さっき 御坂さんを
怒らせてしまっていますし
I did just anger Misaka-san a moment ago.
Okay.
お… おう 待ってろ
Wait here.
（ニセ海原）
うまくいかないものですね
人をダマすのって
Nothing goes as planned, huh?
To lie to someone.
まさか 本物が逃げ出すとは
To think the real one showed up...
You're not... Unabara...
（上条）海原 …じゃないのか？
（ニセ海原）フフフッ…
Magic?
魔術… ンンッ…
（発射音）
くそ！
Damn it!
I see.
（電話の着信音）
なるほど
This Magical Powered Kanamin
pretended to be a student every day...
このマジカルパワード･カナミンは
ふだんは学生に成り済ますことで
ローマ正教が誇る魔女狩り十字軍の
目をごまかしているんだね
...to escape the witch hunting eyes of the Roman Catholic Church's crusaders.
But, what is that rainbow flashing stick?
しかし
あの虹色に光るステッキは 一体？
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）は… はい
（上条）そっちは大丈夫か？
Yes?
Are you okay?!
There's a magician in the city!
町の中に魔術師がいるみたいなんだ
Touma?
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）
当麻？　もしかして追われてるの？
Are you being chased right now?
（上条）ああ
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）特徴は？
Yeah.
What's the person's trait?
服装とか武器とか しぐさとか
His attire, weapon, or actions?
The black stone knife is Obsidian.
黒い石のナイフは黒曜石
多分―
It's probably the Lance of Tlahuixcalpantecuhtli.
トラウィスカルパンテクウトリの
槍(やり)だと思う
（上条）
とら… 何だって？
Tlah- what?
It's the name of an Aztec deity.
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）
もともとは
アステカの神さまの名前だね
That lance will kill anything that absorbs the light of Venus.
その槍は金星の光を浴びた者全てを
殺すといわれているんだよ
Just tell me what I should do now!
（上条）
いいから 今 何をすればいいか
手っとり早く…
お願いですから 一発逆転の
ヒントをください　今すぐに！
Please, just tell me a one-shot understandable hint!
Right away!
The magician's lance is a replica.
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）
魔術師の槍はレプリカ
恐らくは鏡
I think it's a mirror; it reflects the light from Venus and directs it towards the target.
金星の光を黒曜石のナイフで
反射して攻撃しているんだと思う
If you try, I think you can cancel it with your right hand, Touma.
やろうと思えば
当麻の右手でも防げると思うけど
ウワッ！　くそ…
Damn it.
Is the Aztec magic the reason
he has Unabara's appearance?
（上条）
あいつが海原に変装してるのも―
そのアステカの
魔術ってやつなのか？
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）
アステカの神官は
いけにえの皮膚を―
Yes, Aztec priests do have a technique where they wear the flayed skin of sacrifices.
剥いで着る技術があるから
その応用だと思う
I think this is an application of that technique.
Do what with the skin?!
皮膚を… 何だって？
They wear it.
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）
着るの
ナイフでベリベリと剥がして
They use a knife to rip everything off the sacrifice,
If it's just a disguise, then they just need to cut
a little part of the skin and make it into a charm,
変装ってだけなら皮膚をちょっと
切り取って護符を作れば―
and they'll be able to mimic the person's appearance.
姿形をマネることができるね
Damn magicians!
…たく 魔術師ってのは
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）ムッ… 当麻…
（電話を切る音）
Touma-
（ニセ海原）フン！
（上条）ンンッ…
（ニセ海原）
ハハッ… 覚悟してください！
Prepare yourself!
うん？　バカな！
Impossible!
The location and angle to Venus should be flawless!
金星の位置も角度も完璧(かんぺき)なはず
セメントの粉？　くそ…
Cement dust?
Damn it-
All right,
（上条）さぁて 答えてもらうぜ
（ニセ海原）クッ…
time to get some answers out of you.
Why did you pretend to be Unabara?
（上条）
どうして
海原なんかに化けようと考えた？
You're trying to get near Misaka?
御坂に近づくためか？
あいつは魔術とは関係ないだろうが
She has nothing to do with magic!
（ニセ海原）
フッ… あなたは
本当に理解していないんですね
Looks like you really don't get it, eh?
（上条）
なに？
What?
（ニセ海原）
あなたは 10万3,000冊もの
魔道書を占有している
You are in possession of 103,000 grimoires.
その上 魔術師や
レベル５の超能力者など―
On top of that, you even have magicians and Level 5 espers,
people of various talents as your allies, don't you?
多種多様な人材を仲間として
引き入れているじゃないですか
You could even say... that the
Kamijyo faction is gradually forming...
既に “上条勢力”という―
ひとつの団体が
できつつあると言ってもいい
Kamijyo... faction?
（上条）上条 …勢力だと？
（ニセ海原）そう
Yes, a very unstable, but influential, power that
threatens the balance of power of the two worlds.
（ニセ海原）
２つの世界のパワーバランスを
脅かす 不安定で巨大な力
My target is not just you yourself,
but everyone in the Kamijyo faction.
自分の標的は あなた個人ではなく
上条勢力 全員なんです
見知った人間の顔を使って
信頼関係を壊し―
Destroying the relations between faction members by pretending to be someone close...
...to bring down the faction from within.
勢力を内部から切り崩すためにね
You...
（上条）
てめえ…
Unfortunately, Unabara Mitsuki's cover has been blown.
（ニセ海原）
残念ながら 海原光貴は
素性が割れてしまいました
I must obtain my next "face".
次の顔を
手に入れなければなりません
Don't tell me...
まさか 御坂の顔を…
You were going to use Misaka's face-
Screw-
（上条）ふざけ…
（ニセ海原）では―
Then why don't I take your face instead?!
あなたの顔を
いただくとしましょうかね
I thought I could've been friends with you.
（上条）
お前とは
友達になれると思ってたんだぜ
That thought never crossed my mind for a single second.
（ニセ海原）
自分は たった一度でも―
そんなことを
思ったことはありませんよ
Too bad.
（上条）
残念だよ
The time when you were talking about Misaka was also a lie, huh?
お前が御坂の話をしてたときの
あれも―
ただのニセモノだったってこと
なんだろう？
（ニセ海原）
ニセモノじゃダメなんですか？
What's wrong with it being a lie?
What's wrong with a lie trying to protect Misaka-san?
ニセモノが御坂さんを守りたいって
思っちゃいけないんですか？
I didn't want to do this either!
自分だって
こんなマネは したくなかった！
But the Kamijyo faction is too dangerous;
that's what the higher-ups have determined!
でも 上条勢力は危険だと
上が判断してしまったから！
（上条）
お前…
You...
Had you stayed put...
（ニセ海原）
あなたが穏便でいてくれたら―
If they'd told me that you're no problem,
問題なしって報告させてくれたら
静かに引き下がれたのに
I would've retreated peacefully.
I wouldn't have needed to lie to Misaka-san!
御坂さんを
ダマすなんてしなくて済んだのに！
You... really like Misaka-san?
（上条）
お前
本当に御坂のことが好きなのか？
Yeah...
But I've become your enemy now.
でも 自分は あなたたちの
敵になってしまいました
Then, that leaves me no choice.
（上条）
だったら しかたねえ
殺してやるよ
I will kill... that illusion of yours!
お前の その幻想を！
（ニセ海原）ヤーッ！
（上条）ウワッ…
アアッ…
（上条）よけろ！
Move!!!
Have I... lost?
自分は負けたんですか？
さあね
Beats me.
（ニセ海原）
恐らく 攻撃は
今回かぎりでは終わりません
I'm sure this won't be the only assault on you.
You and Misaka-san will continue to be targeted.
あなたや御坂さんは
これからも狙われ続ける
Could you protect her?
守ってもらえますか？　御坂さんを
Protect Misaka-san?
Run to her wherever and whenever...
いつでも どこでも駆けつけて
彼女を守ってくれると―
Promise me you'll protect her?
約束してくれますか？
Geez...
まったく… 最低の返事だ
The worst answer I could expect...
あいつは無自覚で
ああいうことを言うヤツなのよ
He's the kind of person who would say such irresponsible things!
It's not like I'm special to him or anything!
別に
私が特別ってわけじゃないんだから
I know I'm misunderstanding, but...
勘違いって分かってんだけど…
紛らわしいのよ あのバカ
...it's so misleading!
～♪
That idiot...
Next Episode
（上条）
アクセラレータの前に現れた
謎の少女
The mysterious girl that appeared before Accelerator.
彼女が語る衝撃の事実に
彼がとった選択とは…
With the shocking truth she brings with her,
what's the action he decides to take?
次回 「打ち止め(ラストオーダー)」
Next time, "Last Order".
When science and magic cross paths,
科学と魔術が交差するとき
物語は始まる
this epic will begin!